SPEAKER 1: Now that you've initialized
the board and that you've drawn it,
it's time to let the user edit
it and make their moves.
So in the 15.c function, the program
takes input from the user and then
calls the Move function, passing in the
number of the tile that the user
wants to move.
Now, be careful.
This is the actual number of the tile
and not its actual position.
So you'll need to search for the tile's
position to know where it is.
Now, you should only allow the user
to make a move if it's legal.
A legal move is any tile that is
adjacent to the blank tile.
That means above and below, to
the left, and to the right.
So you'll need to know where
the blank tile is as well.
Now, for every move, you're searching
for the user's tile.
But it's probably not best to search for
the blank tile every time, because
you're doing it every single time
the user wants to move.
So instead, it's best to remember where
the blank tile is, using some
well-named variables.
So once you allow the user to make their
moves, they are well on their
way to winning the game of 15.